[
    {"question": "bits and pieces", "answer": "色んなもの；ほんの一部"},
    {"question": "silver lining", "answer": "（悪い出来事にある）良い側面"},
    {"question": "take sth to heart", "answer": "〜を真剣に受け止める、気にする"},
    {"question": "park sth", "answer": "〜をとりあえずこのままにする"},
    {"question": "by hook or by crook", "answer": "なんとしてでも"},
    {"question": "sense-check", "answer": "ざっくりとしたチェック"},
    {"question": "stumped", "answer": "困惑した、困った"},
    {"question": "circle back to sth/sb", "answer": "〜に戻る、また連絡する"},
    {"question": "hard taskmater", "answer": "（仕事に）厳しい人、要求の高い人"},
    {"question": "night and day", "answer": "全く違う、正反対である"},
    {"question": "burst sb's bubble", "answer": "〜の期待・夢・幻想などを壊す"},
    {"question": "drag sb's name through the mud", "answer": "〜の評判を落とす"},
    {"question": "deep-dive", "answer": "詳細な分析"},
    {"question": "boil down to sth", "answer": "要するに〜が重要（原因）である"},
    {"question": "hit the ground running", "answer": "良いスタートを切る"},
    {"question": "wake up on the wrong side of hte bed", "answer": "機嫌が悪い"},
    {"question": "low-hanging fruit", "answer": "簡単に突破できそうなもの"},
    {"question": "icebreaker", "answer": "お互いを知るための活動"},
    {"question": "mock sth up", "answer": "〜をドラフトする"},
    {"question": "or so", "answer": "〜とかその辺"},

    {"question":"jack-of-all-trades", "answer":"何でもできる人；広く浅くできる人"},
    {"question":"vanilla", "answer":"つまらない、ありきたりな"},
    {"question":"hard-headed", "answer":"頭が固い"},
    {"question":"play devil's advocate", "answer":"あえて批判的になる"},
    {"question":"crystalize sth", "answer":"～を具体化する"},
    {"question":"D and M", "answer":"深くて意味のある話、重要な話"},
    {"question":"people person", "answer":"人当たり良い人、社交的な人"},
    {"question":"get sth overthe line", "answer":"～を終わらせる"},
    {"question":"branch out", "answer":"新しいことを始める、手を広げる"},
    {"question":"out of pocket", "answer":"自腹で"},
    {"question":"wordsmith sth", "answer":"～の言葉遣いをより良くする"},
    {"question":"water down", "answer":"（内容などが）薄められた"},
    {"question":"fish for compliments", "answer":"（間接的に）ほめてもらおうとする"},
    {"question":"meet sb halfway", "answer":"～と譲歩する、妥協する"},
    {"question":"weed out sth/sb", "answer":"～を取り除く、排除する"},
    {"question":"better half", "answer":"パートナー、配偶者"},
    {"question":"hit pause", "answer":"一時中断する"},
    {"question":"wind down", "answer":"徐々に終わりに近づく；くつろぐ"},
    {"question":"make a killing", "answer":"大儲けする"},
    {"question":"take a tab in the dark", "answer":"（適当に）推測する、当ててみる"},

    {"question": "take sth with a grain of salt", "answer": "～を話半分に聞く、鵜吞みにしない"},
    {"question": "unwritten rule", "answer": "暗黙の了解、暗黙のルール"},
    {"question": "treading water", "answer": "足踏みする、進歩がない"},
    {"question": "grunt work", "answer": "単調でつまらない仕事"},
    {"question": "hold one's cards close to one chest", "answer": "秘密にする、手の内を隠す"},
    {"question": "unheard of", "answer": "聞いたことがない、珍しい"},
    {"question": "put sb's name in the hat", "answer": "立候補する"},
    {"question": "out of sb's league", "answer": "～には不釣り合いな"},
    {"question": "think back to sth", "answer": "～を思い出す"},
    {"question": "leave sb high and dry", "answer": "～を置いてきぼりにする、見捨てる"},
    {"question": "lucky break", "answer": "幸運、ラッキーな出来事"},
    {"question": "put my best foot forward", "answer": "とにかく全力を尽くす"},
    {"question": "have the final say", "answer": "最終的な決定権を持つ"},
    {"question": "blow it", "answer": "だめである、しくじる"},
    {"question": "fit like a glove", "answer": "ぴったり合う"},
    {"question": "quit while sb is ahead", "answer": "勝っているうちにやめる"},
    {"question": "turn it around", "answer": "（状況を）好転させる"},
    {"question": "show one's hand", "answer": "手の内を見せる"},
    {"question": "circa", "answer": "大体"},
    {"question": "jazz sth up", "answer": "～を明るく盛る、飾る"},

    {"question": "stick out like a sore thumb", "answer": "（悪い意味で）目立つ"},
    {"question": "born with a silver spoon in one's hand", "answer": "（裕福な家庭に）生まれる"},
    {"question": "touch-and-go", "answer": "どうなるか分からない"},
    {"question": "bounce", "answer": "行く"},
    {"question": "up and running", "answer": "（機械などが）動いている"},
    {"question": "dirty laundry", "answer": "恥ずかしい秘密"},
    {"question": "rock the boat", "answer": "波風を立てる"},
    {"question": "give the green light", "answer": "ゴーサインを出す、許可する"},
    {"question": "set in stone", "answer": "（予定が）変更不可能な、確定した"},
    {"question": "backhanded comliment", "answer": "皮肉的なお世辞、ほめ殺し"},
    {"question": "sing sb's praises", "answer": "～をほめちぎる"},
    {"question": "props to sb", "answer": "～に感謝"},
    {"question": "with a clean slate", "answer": "～から、白紙の状態から"},
    {"question": "chip on one's shoulder", "answer": "イライラ、けんか腰"},
    {"question": "chop-chop", "answer": "早く"},
    {"question": "cool as a cucumber", "answer": "とても落ち着いている"},
    {"question": "knuckle down", "answer": "真面目に取り組む、集中する"},
    {"question": "takeaway", "answer": "重要なポイント"},
    {"question": "recap", "answer": "おさらい"},
    {"question": "ring a bell", "answer": "ピンとくる、心当たりがある"},

    {"question": "call a spade a spade", "answer": "言うことをはっきり言う"},
    {"question": "front-load sth", "answer": "～を前倒しでやる"},
    {"question": "drip-feed sth", "answer": "（少しずつ）～を上げる、わたす"},
    {"question": "wild goose chase", "answer": "あてもなく行うこと"},
    {"question": "spruce sth/sb up", "answer": "～をきれいにする"},
    {"question": "walk in sb's shoes", "answer": "～の気持ちになる、の立場で考える"},
    {"question": "spin wheels", "answer": "無駄な努力をする"},
    {"question": "talk down to sb", "answer": "～を見下すような感じで話す"},
    {"question": "full of oneself", "answer": "自己中心的である"},
    {"question": "snapshot", "answer": "わかりやすく表したもの"},
    {"question": "like pulling teeth", "answer": "非常に困難なことである"},
    {"question": "pull the trigger", "answer": "（思い切って）決断を下す"},
    {"question": "sketchy", "answer": "怪しい"},
    {"question": "everything under the sun", "answer": "ありとあらゆるもの・こと"},
    {"question": "go-ahead", "answer": "ゴーサイン、許可"},
    {"question": "ramp up sth", "answer": "～を増加する"},
    {"question": "play it by ear", "answer": "臨機応変にやる、そのとき考える"},
    {"question": "sugarcoat sth", "answer": "～をオブラートに包む"},
    {"question": "OCD", "answer": "かなり細かい人、潔癖症"},
    {"question": "two sides of the same coin", "answer": "表裏一体"}
]